USS Arizona Collection, 1907-2015 (bulk 1915-1941)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 1: Photographic Materials, 1915-1962
  - Subseries 2: USS Arizona and Personnel Photographs, 1916-1941
    - Sailors Standing Outside Coconut Grove, Panama, 71-1-235, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Four Sailors inside Bar, Panama, 71-1-236, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Four Sailors inside Bar, Panama, 71-1-237, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - William A. Watkins and Donald Barley on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-11C, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - William A. Watkins in Scuba Gear as 2nd Class Deep Sea Diver with Sailors in Uniform, 77-3-63, circa 1934-1938 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - William A. Watkins in Scuba Gear as 2nd Class Deep Sea Diver, 77-3-64, circa 1934-1938 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - William A. Watkins Holding Pots on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-65, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - William A. Watkins Holding Brooms and Dustpan on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-66, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - William A. Watkins on Dock Sitting on Wooden Beam, 77-3-67, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - William A. Watkins Posing with Pipe on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-68, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - William A. Watkins Posing with a No Parking Sign on Base, 77-3-69, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - William A. Watkins Posing in Front of Garden Archway on Base, 77-3-70, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - William A. Watkins on Base Sitting on Grass, 77-3-71, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - William A. Watkins Sitting in Front of Doorway on Base, 77-3-72, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - William A. Watkins Posing in Front of a Building on Base, 77-3-73, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - William A. Watkins Posing with Cigarette in Car, 77-3-74, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - William A. Watkins Posing in front of Car, 77-3-75, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - William A. Watkins Posing on Couch, 77-3-76, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - William A. Watkins Posing in front of a Camper, 77-3-77, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - William A. Watkins and Unidentified Sailor Mopping, 77-3-78, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - William A. Watkins and Two Unidentified Sailors Sitting on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-79, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - William A. Watkins and Unidentified Sailor on Dock, 77-3-80, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - William A. Watkins and Two Unidentified Sailors Posing with Cigarettes, 77-3-81, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - William A. Watkins and Unidentified Sailor at Entrance to the Hostess House and Library, 77-3-82, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - William A. Watkins and Unidentified Sailor on USS Arizona, 77-3-83, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - William A. Watkins and Unidentified Sailor on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-84, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - William A. Watkins and Three Unidentified Sailors Posing with a Dog in Front of a Fire Truck, 77-3-85, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - William A. Watkins and Six Unidentified Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-86, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - William A. Watkins and Group of Sailors on Dock, 77-3-87, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Holding up William A. Watkins, 77-3-88, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - William A. Watkins and Unidentified Sailor in front of Anchor Chains on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-89, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - William A. Watkins with Unidentified Woman, 77-3-90, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Photo Booth Photograph of Unidentified Woman, 77-3-91, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Photo Booth Photograph of Unidentified Woman, 77-3-92, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified House Exterior, 77-3-93, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Three Men Leaning Against Car with Woods in the Background, 77-3-94, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Two Men Sitting on a Bench with the Woods In the Background, 77-3-95, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified Farm Exterior, 77-3-96, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified Farm Exterior with Stream in Foreground, 77-3-97, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - William A. Watkins with Horse, 77-3-98, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Boy with Horse with Barn in Background, 77-3-99, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - William A. Watkins in Fire Truck on Base, 77-3-100, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Motorcycle and Car in front of House, 77-3-101, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Unidentified Man, 77-3-102, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Unidentified Woman in Yard, 77-3-103, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Unidentified Man in Garden, 77-3-104, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Unidentified Woman, 77-3-105, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Man Playing Fiddle and William A. Watkins Playing Mandolin, 77-3-106, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Unidentified Man Washing a Car, 77-3-107, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Unidentified Man Sitting on Car Drinking Out of a Bottle, 77-3-108, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Sailor in Overalls Leaning on a Truck, 77-3-109, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Unidentified Man Standing in a Field, 77-3-110, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Unidentified Man Standing in Front of Door, 77-3-111, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Young Boy Standing in Field, 77-3-112, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Unidentified Farm Exterior with Stream in Foreground, 77-3-113, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Unidentified Man and Woman Sitting on a Car, 77-3-114, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Unidentified Woman Standing in front of House, 77-3-115, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Two Men Standing in the Woods, 77-3-116, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Two Men on Bikes in front of Building, 77-3-117, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Two Men on Bikes in front of Building, 77-3-118, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Unidentified Man Holding Baby, 77-3-119, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Jim, 77-3-120, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - USS Arizona Football Team, 77-3-121, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Captain Charles S. Red Mike Freeman, 77-3-122, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Captain Freeman and Commander Best, Navigator, 77-3-123, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Two Unidentified Policemen, 77-3-124, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified Policeman Sitting on Fence, 77-3-125, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Rifle Practice in a Field, 77-3-126, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Portrait of Unidentified Sailor, 77-3-127, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Portrait of Unidentified Sailor, 77-3-128, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Portrait of Unidentified Sailor, 77-3-129, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Three Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-130, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Two Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-131, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Three Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-132, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified Sailor with Broom and Mop on deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-133, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Four Unidentified Sailors on Fire Truck, 77-3-134, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Four Unidentified Sailors on Fire Truck, 77-3-134 (Duplicate of 77-3-134), circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Fire Truck, 77-3-136, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Fire Truck, 77-3-137 (Duplicate of 77-3-136), circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Fire Truck, 77-3-138, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Fire Truck, 77-3-139, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Unidentified Sailor Leaning on Fire truck, 77-3-140, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors Lying on Deck of USS Arizona beneath Gun, 77-3-141, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors Posing with Mops on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-142, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors on Dock, 77-3-143, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors in Uniform on Dock, 77-3-144, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors in Uniform on Base, 77-3-145, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Five Unidentified Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-146, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Base, 77-3-147, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Base, 77-3-148, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Base, 77-3-149, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Four Unidentified Sailors Posing with Mops on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-150, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Four Unidentified Sailors Posing in front of Building on Base, 77-3-151, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Base, 77-3-152, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Base Leaning on a Pole, 77-3-153, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Base Leaning on a Pole, 77-3-154, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing in front of Building on Base, 77-3-155, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified Sailor Holding Puppy on Base, 77-3-156, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Four Unidentified Sailors Standing Outside of House on Base, 77-3-157, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Shorty Carver on Base, 77-3-158, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Morgan Hunoley and Unidentified Sailor on Base, 77-3-159, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - A Messy Cook, 77-3-160, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Two Puppies on Base, 77-3-161, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Four Unidentified Sailors on Base, 77-3-162, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Base, 77-3-163, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing in front of Building on Base, 77-3-164, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Two Sailors Posing with a Rifle and Knife, 77-3-165, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Base Leaning on a Telephone Pole, 77-3-166, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Base, 77-3-167, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Five Unidentified sailors on Base, 77-3-168, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors in Naval Coats on Base, 77-3-169, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - 1st Week Flag Practice on Base, 77-3-170, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Unidentified Sailor Mopping Ground on Base, 77-3-171, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing by Boat #2, 77-3-172, circa 1932 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - USS Arizona Baseball Player, 77-3-173, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified Sailor Smoking a Pipe on Base, 77-3-174, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified Sailor with Rifle, 77-3-175, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Three Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-176, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-177, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Base, 77-3-178, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified Sailor Sitting by #2 Boat, 77-3-179, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Dock, 77-3-180, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-181, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-182, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-183, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified Sailor Sitting on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-184, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-185, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Dock, 77-3-186, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing next to Stop Sign on Base, 77-3-187, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Dock, 77-3-188, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing in front of Mail Box on Base, 77-3-189, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Base, 77-3-190, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors Laying on Ground at Norfolk Training Center, 77-3-191, circa 1930 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Bill on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-192, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors Sitting on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-193, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Leaning on Gun on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-194, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing Between Guns on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-195, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Standing Between Guns on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-196, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Unidentified Sailor Mopping the Deck of the USS Arizona, 77-3-197, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Holding Hats on the Deck of the USS Arizona, 77-3-198, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Overhead Photograph of Two Unidentified Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona,77-3-199, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Two Unidentified Soldiers on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-200, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors Sitting on Dock, 77-3-201, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Unidentified Sailor Sitting on Dock, 77-3-202, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Unidentified Sailor Sitting on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-203, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing Next to Birdbath on Base, 77-3-204, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing on a Rocky Beach, 77-3-205, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-206, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-207, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified Sailor Sitting on Gun on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-208, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors Standing under a Palm Tree, 77-3-209, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Unidentified Sailor Doing Handstand, 77-3-210, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors Play Fighting on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-211, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors Play Fighting on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-211, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors Bending Over on Grass, 77-3-212, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Sitting on Grass, 77-3-213, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors on Dock, 77-3-214, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Unidentified Sailor Sitting on Grass, 77-3-215, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Standing Barefoot on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-216, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Unidentified Sailor, 77-3-217, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Unidentified Sailor Holding Mop, Broom, and Dustpan, 77-3-218, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Four Unidentified Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-219, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Unidentified Sailor on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-220, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Five Unidentified Sailors Goofing Off on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-221, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Unidentified Sailor on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-222, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Unidentified Sailor Sitting on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-223, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Eating on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-224, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Unidentified Sailor Barefoot on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-225, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing Next to Anchor Chain on USS Arizona Deck,77-3-226, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors in front of Fireplace, 77-3-227, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Unidentified Sailor and Unidentified Woman on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-228, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Shirtless Unidentified Sailor on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-229, circa 1932 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Unidentified Sailor Riding Bicycle at Norfolk Training Camp, 77-3-230, circa 1930 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified Sailor Riding Bicycle at Norfolk Training Camp, 77-3-231, circa 1930 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - View of Norfolk Training Camp, 77-3-232, circa 1930 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - View of Norfolk Training Camp, 77-3-233, circa 1930 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - View of Norfolk Training Camp, 77-3-234, circa 1930 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - View of United States Flag on Norfolk Training Camp, 77-3-235, circa 1930 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - USS Arizona Docked, 77-3-236, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - USS Arizona Docked, 77-3-236, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - View of USS Arizona Bow, 77-3-237, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - View of USS Arizona Bow in Dry Dock, 77-3-238, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Waves Hitting Bow of USS Arizona, 77-3-239, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - USS Arizona Docked in Boston, MA, 77-3-240, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, 77-3-241, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - USS Arizona in Norfolk Navy Yard Dry Dock During Modernization, 77-3-242, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - USS Arizona in Wet Dock, 77-3-243, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified Sailors Performing Maintenance on USS Arizona in Dry Dock, 77-3-244, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified Farm, 77-3-245, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Road, 77-3-246, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - View of Hill, 77-3-247, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Exterior of Service School, 77-3-248, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Interior of Service School, 77-3-249, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - View of Street Intersection, 77-3-250, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Unidentified Church, 77-3-251, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Views of Building Taken from the Water, 77-3-252, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - USS Arizona Docked, 77-3-253, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - View of Unidentified Ship on Water Taken from USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-254, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Large Drill in Unidentified Location, 77-3-255, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified Town, 77-3-256, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - View of U.S. Hercules on Water, 77-3-257, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - View of Unidentified Town Taken from Water, 77-3-258, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Pacific Reliance Docked, 77-3-259, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - View of Three Large Antennae Taken from Water, 77-3-260, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - View of Small Island Taken from Water, 77-3-261, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - View of Hill Taken from Water, 77-3-262, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - View of Peninsula Taken from Water, 77-3-263, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - View of House on top of a Hill, 77-3-264, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - USS Wright at Sea, 77-3-265, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified Dock, 77-3-266, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - View of Unidentified Ship taken from Dock, 77-3-267, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Sailor in front of a Cave, 77-3-268, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Sailor Standing in front of a Mountain, 77-3-269, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - View of Unidentified Valley, 77-3-270, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - View of Unidentified Mountain, 77-3-271, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Seagulls in Flight over the Ocean, 77-3-272, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - View of Unidentified Harbor Taken from Water, 77-3-273, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - View of Unidentified Landscape Taken from Water, 77-3-274, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - View of Unidentified Islands Taken from Water, 77-3-275, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - View of Unidentified Ship at Sea, 77-3-276, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - View of Unidentified Boats at Sea, 77-3-277, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Unidentified Boat at Sea, 77-3-278, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Unidentified Sailors on Unidentified Boat, 77-3-279, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Unidentified Sailor in Diving Suit, 77-3-280, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Unidentified Sailor in Diving Suit, 77-3-281, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Exterior of U.S. Navy Operating Base, Hampton Roads, 77-3-283, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - View of Alcatraz, San Francisco, CA, 77-3-284, circa 1932 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Four Unidentified Sailors Mopping the USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-285, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Gunnery Practice, 77-3-286, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Hanging Out Hammocks, 77-3-287, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - View of Small Boat at Sea taken from USS Arizona, 77-3-288, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona Motorboat, 77-3-289, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Two USS Arizona Motorboats and Two Row Boats at Sea, 77-3-290, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona with Seagulls Flying Overhead, 77-3-291, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified Sailors Standing Near Warheads on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-292, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Sailors Hoisting Warheads on USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-293, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - USS Arizona Guns Being Fired, 77-3-294, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - USS Arizona Guns Being Fired, 77-3-295, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Rifle Practice on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-296, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Victorious 1st Division Crew – Defeated 5th for CPO Cup, 1931 July, 77-3-297 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Three Unidentified Soldiers Standing with CPO Cup and Trophy, 77-3-298, circa 1931 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - CPO Cup, 77-3-299, circa 1931 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - CPO Cup, Prize for Whaleboat Race, 77-3-300, circa 1931 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Assortment of Trophies on Display on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-301, circa 1931 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Commanding Officers Posing on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-302, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Entire USS Arizona Crew, 77-3-303, circa 1932 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Unidentified Sailor Posing with James Cagney on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-304, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Unidentified Sailor with Unidentified Officer on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-305, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - James Cagney and Gloria Stuart Filming a Scene from Here Comes the Navy on the USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-306, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - James Cagney and Gloria Stuart Filming a Scene from Here Comes the Navy on the USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-307, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Unidentified Officer and Unidentified Sailor on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-308, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-309, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Unidentified Sailor Posing with James Cagney on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-310, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Posing with James Cagney on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-311, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Unidentified Sailor Posing with James Cagney on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-312, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Unidentified Sailor and Gloria Stuart posing on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-313, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Unidentified Sailor and Unidentified Woman on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-314, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Unidentified 1934 Battle Fleet Rower and Sailor on set of Here Comes the Navy,77-3-315, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 31)